U-TURN, YOU DIE!
Trucks is a horror, science fiction, thriller film directed by Chris Thomson.
A group of seemingly humanistic trucks takeover a truck
stop and starts killing everything in sight.
The remaining townsfolk must band together and come up with a way to murder the inanimate
objects, a seemingly difficult task considering the abnormal circumstances.
Ray, played by Timothy Busfield.
Hope, played by Brenda Bakke.
Trucker Bob, played by Aidan Devine.
Jack, played by Jay Brazeau.
Logan, played by Brendan Fletcher.
Abby, played by Amy Stewart.
Trucks is a 1997 horror television film directed by Chris Thomson, which follows the story of a group of
tourists and locals attacked by autonomous trucks and other inexplicable phenomena in a rural town.
It is based on Stephen King's short story "Trucks", which also served as the
source material for Maximum Overdrive, the only film directed by King.
Trucks aired on the USA Network on October 29, 1997.
The film explores themes of man vs machine, truck, based on short story.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.